All right, we're going to go back a
little bit in time to our discussion
about variables. In the video where I
talk about variables, I relate variables
to a box. You may notice this box is a
different box than I used in those
videos. Um, we're going to say this
experience is similar to swapping the
actor between for War Machine between
Iron Man one and Iron Man 2. Um, so this
is a variable. I told you a variable can
hold information.
Um, so let's say I took a piece of paper
and I wrote some information on it. I on
this one I wrote my name. This is
similar to storing a string. Um, this
string um, it just stores information.
This piece of paper all it's doing is
storing that string information that I
wrote.
I also have a phone here. A phone is
similar to a function. So when I told
you a function could do three things. It
can take some input. It can do some work
and it gives give some output. Um, this
phone can do three things. I can give it
some input by typing on the keyboard
keyboard. I can hit the search function
and it will do some work. It'll search
and then it will return information.
It'll give me back results that I can
use. So, if we relate this phone to a
function um can take input, do some work
and give some output. Now, let's go back
to this string. This string is just
storing information. Um, does this piece
of paper take input, do work, and give
output? Not really. It just stores
information. So, in the past, what
you've been doing is you've been
creating variables. And this variable
can hold information. It's just a box
and it's a storage location. So, if I
take a string and I put it in the
variable, then I say, what's in this
variable? Well, it's the string I just
put inside there. What I'm going to show
you in the next video is that rather
than just putting strings in boxes, you
can also put entire functions in boxes.
So now if I ask you what's in this box,
my entire phone function is in this